(Howard:)Hey, can I come in?
(Sheldon:)Apparently any man
is welcome in this house.
(Sheldon:)Why not you?
(Sheldon:)I thought you were waiting
in the car.
(Howard:)That was an hour ago, Sheldon.
(Howard:)A Jew sits in front of a house
in Texas that long,
"For Sale" signs start to go up.
(Howard:)I take it things didn't
go smoothly with your mom.
(Raj:)No.
(Sheldon:)I'm not sure how we're going
to get past this.
You know, I sort of went
through something like this myself.
(Sheldon:)Howard, we've all seen
your mother naked.
(Sheldon:)That woman needs to learn
how to tie a robe.
(Howard:)I'm talking about when
my mom started seeing someone
a couple years after my dad left.
(Sheldon:)I didn't know she did.
(Howard:)Yeah, she was dating this guy,
(Howard:)and I was kind of a jerk
to her about it.